

### Yuri Pereira Front-end Developer

## My Objective

I am a person who is always looking for something new. I founded an online consulting firm in September 2014 aimed at changing the practices of the middle Health & Fitness in digital media and live new challenging experiences. Currently focused on absorbing knowledge MVW framework Angular.js and best web practices in addition to being front-end developer for over 4 years.

#### Education

Computer Systems [August 2015 - Curently]

Federal University Fluminense- UFF

Computer Science [August 2010 - January 2015]

federal University of Rio De Janeiro - UFRJ

Technical School in Data Processing [January 2006- December 2008] Senhora da Pena High School

# Professional Experience

Trainee Full-Stack Web Developer [Janeiro 2015 - atualmente]

One of maintenance project leaders of the channels TV GLOBOSAT group. My role include create new features and hotfixes for every ongoing projects of GLOBOSAT, such as: Channel Sexy Hot, GNT, Multishow, among others.

Web Project Leader [June 2014 - August 2015]

Act as leader of the new project CAPGOV, collaborating to create a new page into the context of current technologies and improving the position on google by SEO. Using drupal CMS as content manager.

Intern Web Developer [February 2011 - June 2014]

CAPGOV - COPPE - UFRJ

### Skills

Proficiency	Professional
HTML5/CSS	Web design
Bootstrap	Programming
Photoshop	TDD
PHP/SQL	Personal
Javascript	Creative
Gulp/Tasks	Leadership
Python	Team

# Personal Information

Name Yuri Pereira Ramos

Birth 12 de Junho de 1991

**Nacionality** Brazilian

Nationality Rio de Janeiro

Languages English(fluent), Spanish

(intermediate), Portuguese

# **Recently Projects**

ElementoArt

I worked in the development of front-end and some layers of the back-end.

Startup of a social network Live-streaming.

# Highlights

- Self-Didact
- **Good Oratory**
- Sociability
- **Proactivity**
- Ágile Development (Methodologies Scrum e Kanban)

#### Contact

Address Av. Prefeito Dulcidio Cardoso, 2500, bloco 2 apto 1501.

+5521 97141-7218

Phone

Email yuri.pramos@gmail.com

Web www.yuriramos.com